Guide to the Papers of Lourdes Portillo, 1979¯2001 M1480
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1: Paper Production Materials, 1979¯2001
  - Other Projects
    - Sundance Film Festival, Park City, Utah, 1/1997; 1.0 Items (Carton 117, Folder 32)
    - Toronto International Film Festival ¯ Delegate List, 1997; 1.0 Items (Carton 117, Folder 33)
    - Visiting Artist Program, University of Colorado at Boulder, 1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 117, Folder 34)
    - Worldwide Roundup of 1975 Film Festivals & Conferences, 7/1975; 1.0 Items (Carton 117, Folder 35)
    - American Film ¯ Magazine of the Film and Television Arts ¯ Volume X, #7, 5/1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 1)
    - Basta! La Historia de Nuestra Lucha ¯ Enough! The Tale of Our Struggle; Farm Worker Press, Inc., Delano, CA, 1966; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 2)
    - Cinema 2002, Madrid, Spain ¯ #58, 12/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 3)
    - Cinema News ¯ Foundation For Art in Cinema, San Anselmo, CA ¯ #78 ¯ 3 & 4, 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 4)
    - Cinemas d'Amerique Latine, Toulouse, France ¯ #1, 3/1993; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 5)
    - Cinemas d'Amerique Latine, Toulouse, France ¯ #4, 1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 6)
    - Cineaste, New York, New York ¯ Vol. XX, No. 2, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 7)
    - Cineaste, New York, New York ¯ Vol. XIII, No. 1, 1983; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 8)
    - Cineaste, New York, New York ¯ Vol. XIV, No. 1, 1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 9)
    - Cinemateca Revista, Uruguay, 12/1992; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 10)
    - El Amante Cine, Argentina ¯ No. 77 ¯ July/August 1998, 8/1998; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 11)
    - El Amante Cine, Argentina ¯ No. 72, 2/1998; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 12)
    - El Amante Cine, Argentina ¯ No. 66, 8/1997; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 13)
    - El Amante Cine, Argentina ¯ No. 57, 11/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 14)
    - El Amante Cine, Argentina ¯ No. 56, 10/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 15)
    - El Amante Cine, Argentina ¯ No. 55, 9/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 16)
    - El Amante Cine, Argentina ¯ No. 54, 8/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 17)
    - El Amante Cine, Argentina ¯ No. 53, 7/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 18)
    - El Amante Cine, Argentina ¯ No. 52, 6/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 19)
    - El Amante Cine, Argentina ¯ No. 51, 5/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 20)
    - El Amante Cine, Argentina ¯ No. 71, 1/1998; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 21)
    - Festival Latino in New York (Joseph Papp Presents), 1989; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 22)
    - Film Comment ¯ Published by the Film Society of Licoln Center, New York ¯ Vol. 21, #2 ¯ March/April 1985, 4/1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 23)
    - Film Comment, New York ¯ Vol. 31, #2 ¯ March/April 1995, 4/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 24)
    - Film Comment, New York, 6/1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 25)
    - 17th San Francisco International Lesbian & Gay Film Festival, 1993; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 26)
    - The Independent Film & Video Monthly, New York, 3/1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 27)
    - The Independent Film & Video Monthly, New York ¯ July/August 1985, 8/1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 28)
    - The Independent Film & Video Monthly, New York, 6/1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 29)
    - The Independent Film & Video Monthly, New York, 3/1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 30)
    - The Independent Film & Video Monthly, New York ¯ January/February 1985, 2/1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 31)
    - Latin American Visions, Philadelphia, PA (2 Copies), 1989; 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 32)
    - Sight & Sound International Film Quarterly, London, England ¯ Vol. 52, #1 ¯ Winter 1982/1983, 1.0 Items (Carton 118, Folder 33)
- Series 2: Audio Visual Materials, 1979¯2001
  - Despues de Terremoto, 1979
    - After the Earthquake, nd; 1.0 Items; Video: VHS; Dub; 60 min (Carton 56, Videotape 1)
    - Despues del Terremoto, nd; 1.0 Items; Video: DVD¯Recordable; Dub; 120 min (Carton 56, Item 2)
    - Tape I, nd; 1.0 Items; Video: 1/2" open reel video; Master; 1210 ft. (Carton 56, Item 3)
    - Despues del Temblor/ After the Earthquake ¯ rehearsal of scenes, nd; 1.0 Items; Video: 1/2" open reel video; Dub; 2 min; 380 ft. (Carton 56, Item 4)
    - No Title, nd; 1.0 Items; Audio: Full coat Super8 Sound; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 5)
    - Despues del Terremoto Tape Roll #1, 4/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 6)
    - Despues del Terremoto Tape Roll #2, 4/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 7)
    - Despues del Terremoto Tape Roll #3, 4/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 8)
    - Despues del Terremoto Tape Roll #4, 4/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 9)
    - Despues del Terremoto Tape Roll #5, 4/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 10)
    - Despues del Terremoto Tape Roll #6, 4/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 11)
    - Despues del Terremoto Tape Roll #7, 4/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 12)
    - Despues del Terremoto Tape Roll #8, 4/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 13)
    - Despues del Terremoto Tape Roll #9, 4/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 14)
    - Despues del Terremoto Tape Roll #10, 4/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 15)
    - Despues del Terremoto Tape Roll #11, 4/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 16)
    - Despues del Terremoto Tape Roll #12, 4/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 17)
    - Despues del Terremoto Tape Roll #13, 4/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 18)
    - Despues del Terremoto Tape Roll #15, 4/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 19)
    - Despues del Terremoto Tape Roll #16, 4/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 20)
    - Despues del Terremoto Tape Roll #17, 4/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 21)
    - Despues del Terremoto Tape Roll #18, 4/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 22)
    - Despues del Terremoto Tape Roll #19, 4/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 23)
    - Despues del Terremoto Tape Roll #20, 4/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 24)
    - Despues del Terremoto Tape Roll #21, 4/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 25)
    - Despues del Terremoto Tape Roll #22, 4/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 26)
    - Despues del Terremoto Tape Roll #23 ¯ Origianl sound track of fine cut, 4/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 27)
    - Fine cut ¯ final transfer: Dialogue for Subtitles, 8/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 28)
    - Lourdes AFI Film Roll #1¯Wild, 8/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 29)
    - Lourdes AFI Film Roll #2¯Wild, 8/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 30)
    - Lourdes AFI Film Wild fx Roll #3¯W, 1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 31)
    - Despues del Terramoto Wild fx ¯ Roll #4¯W, 9/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 32)
    - Despues del Terramoto Wild fx ¯ Roll #5¯W, 9/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 33)
    - Despues del Terramoto Wild fx ¯ Roll #6¯W, 9/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 34)
    - Despues del Terramoto Wild fx ¯ Roll #7¯W, 9/1978; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 56, Item 35)
    - Music/Effects Track 3, nd; 1.0 Items; Film and Audio: Pix and Track mixed with fullcoat 16mm; Master; ~1000 ft. (Carton 56, Reel 36)
    - Music Track 4, nd; 1.0 Items; Film and Audio: Pix and Track mixed with fullcoat 16mm; Master; ~1000 ft. (Carton 56, Reel 37)
    - Effects Track 7, nd; 1.0 Items; Film and Audio: Pix and Track mixed with fullcoat 16mm; Master; ~1000 ft. (Carton 56, Reel 38)
    - Despues del Terremoto, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: 16mm Pix and Sound; Print; ~1000 ft. (Carton 56, Reel 39)
    - An Improbable Journey, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: 16mm Pix and Sound; Print; ~1000 ft. (Carton 56, Reel 40)
    - "Terremoto" Original B&W Rolls 1¯4, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: 16mm B&W Negative; Outs; 700 ft. (Carton 110, Reel 1)
    - "Terremoto" Original B&W Rolls 5¯7, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: 16mm B&W Negative; Outs; 700 ft. (Carton 110, Reel 2)
    - "Terremoto" Original B&W Rolls 16¯18, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: 16mm B&W Negative; Outs; 900 ft. (Carton 110, Reel 3)
    - "Terremoto" Original B&W Rolls 19¯21, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: 16mm B&W Negative; Outs; 700 ft. (Carton 110, Reel 4)
    - "Terremoto" Original B&W Rolls 22¯25, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: 16mm B&W Negative; Outs; 1000 ft. (Carton 110, Reel 5)
    - "Terremoto" Original B&W Rolls 26¯28, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: 16mm B&W Negative; Outs; 800 ft. (Carton 110, Reel 6)
    - "Terremoto" Original B&W "A" Roll, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: 16mm B&W Negative; Outs; 875 ft. (Carton 110, Reel 7)
    - "Terremoto" Original B&W "B" Roll, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: 16mm B&W Negative; Outs; 875 ft. (Carton 110, Reel 8)
    - "Terremoto" Cut Workprint, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: 16mm B&W Negative; Outs; 900 ft. (Carton 110, Reel 9)
    - "Terremoto" Original B&W Camera Rolls 1¯4, nd; 1.0 Items; Film; 16mm B&W Picture Negative; 350 ft. (Carton 111, Reel 1)
    - "Terremoto" Original B&W Camera Rolls 22¯28, nd; 1.0 Items; Film; 16mm B&W Picture Negative; 200 ft. (Carton 111, Reel 2)
    - "Terremoto" Original B&W Camera Rolls 5¯7, nd; 1.0 Items; Film; 16mm B&W Picture Negative; 375 ft. (Carton 111, Reel 3)
    - "Terremoto" Original B&W Camera Rolls 8¯15, nd; 1.0 Items; Film; 16mm B&W Picture Negative; 375 ft. (Carton 111, Reel 4)
    - "Terremoto" Original B&W Camera Rolls 16¯21, nd; 1.0 Items; Film; 16mm B&W Picture Negative; 500 ft. (Carton 111, Reel 5)
    - Portillo R¯1, nd; 1.0 Items; Film; 16mm Color Silent Positive; 75 ft. (Carton 111, Reel 6)
    - Portillo R¯2, nd; 1.0 Items; Film; 16mm Color Silent Positive; 650 ft. (Carton 111, Reel 7)
    - "Despues del Terremoto" B&W Transfer, nd; 1.0 Items; Film; 16mm B&W Positive w/ Optical Sound; Transfer; 800 ft. (Carton 111, Reel 8)
    - "After the Earthquake" Center Track, nd; 1.0 Items; Audio: 16mm Full Coat Mag; Dub; 1000 ft. (Carton 111, Reel 9)
    - "Despues del Terremoto" Print #21381¯01¯02, nd; 1.0 Items; Film; 16mm B&W Positive w/ Optical Sound; Exhibition Print; 1000 ft. (Carton 111, Reel 10)
  - Las Madres: The Mothers of Plaza de Mayo, 1986
    - 64 ¯ "Las Madres" Stills R3, 7/1985; 1.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Color Negative; 365 ft. (Carton 100, Reel 12)
    - 76 ¯ "Argentina" R 85¯2, 6/1985; 1.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 100, Reel 13)
    - 39 ¯ "Las Madres" R 9, 1/1985; 1.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 100, Reel 14)
    - 84 ¯ "Argentina" R 59, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 100, Reel 15)
    - [unknown title], nd; 1.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 100, Reel 16)
    - 14: "Argentina" Roll 85¯4, 6/1985; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 101, Reel 1)
    - 31: "Argentina" Roll 33, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 101, Reel 2)
    - 40: "Argentina" Roll 55, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 101, Reel 3)
    - 42: "Argentina" Roll 48, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 101, Reel 4)
    - 43: "Argentina" Roll 49, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 101, Reel 5)
    - 44: "Argentina" Roll 39, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 101, Reel 6)
    - 47: "Argentina" Roll 30, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 101, Reel 7)
    - 48: "Argentina" Roll 21, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 101, Reel 8)
    - 50: "Argentina" Roll 36, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 101, Reel 9)
    - 51: "Argentina" Roll 38, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 101, Reel 10)
    - 53: "Argentina" Roll 5, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 101, Reel 11)
    - 54: "Argentina" Roll 4, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 101, Reel 12)
    - 57: "Argentina" Roll 56, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 101, Reel 13)
    - 58: "Argentina" Roll 45, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 101, Reel 14)
    - 59: "Argentina" Roll 43, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 101, Reel 15)
    - 60: "Argentina" Roll 42, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 101, Reel 16)
    - 8: "Argentina" Roll 51, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 102, Reel 1)
    - 12: "Argentina" Roll 57, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 102, Reel 2)
    - 30: "Argentina" Roll 47, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 102, Reel 3)
    - 55: "Argentina" Roll 6, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 102, Reel 4)
    - 56: "Argentina" Roll 3, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 102, Reel 5)
    - 66: "Las Madres" #2, 1/1985; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 102, Reel 6)
    - 67: [unknown title], nd; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 102, Reel 7)
    - 68: "Las Madres" Roll 5, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 102, Reel 8)
    - 70: "Argentina" Roll 19, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 102, Reel 9)
    - 71: "Argentina" Roll 15, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 102, Reel 10)
    - 72: "Argentina" Roll 14, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 102, Reel 11)
    - 100: [unknown title], nd; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; 16mm; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 102, Reel 12)
    - "Las Madres", nd; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Trims; 16mm; Color Negative; 75 ft. (Carton 102, Reel 13)
    - Clean Slate Productions Workprint for Opt. Layout, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: Work Print; 16mm; Color Negative; 30 ft & 50 ft. (2 reels) (Carton 102, Reel 14, 15)
    - Subtitle Outs: 16 ¯ 44240, 17 ¯ 44460, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: Subtitle Outs; 16mm; Black and White Negative; 350 ft. & 250 ft. (Carton 102, Reel 16, 17)
    - 1: "Argentina" Roll 23, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 103, Reel 1)
    - 2: "Argentina" Roll 17, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 103, Reel 2)
    - 3: "Argentina" Roll 27, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 103, Reel 3)
    - 4: "Argentina" Roll 24, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 103, Reel 4)
    - 5: "Argentina" Roll 25, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 103, Reel 5)
    - 6: "Argentina" Roll 28, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 103, Reel 6)
    - 7: "Argentina" Roll 13, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 103, Reel 7)
    - 9: "Argentina" Roll 53, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 103, Reel 8)
    - 10: "Argentina" Roll 50, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 103, Reel 9)
    - 11: "Argentina" Roll 54, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 103, Reel 10)
    - 13: "Argentina" Roll 85¯5, 6/1985; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 103, Reel 11)
    - 15: "Argentina" Roll 85¯3, 6/1985; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 103, Reel 12)
    - 16: "Argentina" Roll 85¯6, 6/1985; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 103, Reel 13)
    - 17: "Argentina" Roll 85¯1, 6/1985; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 103, Reel 14)
    - 18: "Argentina" Roll 35, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 103, Reel 15)
    - 19: "Argentina" Roll 41, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 103, Reel 16)
    - 22: "Argentina" Roll 22, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 104, Reel 1)
    - 23: "Argentina" Roll 2, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 104, Reel 2)
    - 24: "Argentina" Roll 16, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 104, Reel 3)
    - 25: "Argentina" Roll 20, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 104, Reel 4)
    - 26: "Argentina" Roll 52, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 104, Reel 5)
    - 27: "Las Madres" Roll #3, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 104, Reel 6)
    - 28: Roll #1 ¯ Stills, 7/1985; 1.0 Items; Film: Stills; Black and White; 400 ft. (Carton 104, Reel 7)
    - 29: Roll #2 ¯ Stills, 7/1985; 1.0 Items; Film: Stills; Black and White; 400 ft. (Carton 104, Reel 8)
    - 32: "Argentina" Roll 1, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 104, Reel 9)
    - 33: "Argentina" Roll 44, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 104, Reel 10)
    - 34: "Argentina" Roll 32, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 104, Reel 11)
    - 35: "Las Madres" Roll 8, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 75 ft. (Carton 104, Reel 12)
    - 36: "Argentina" Roll 8, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 104, Reel 13)
    - 37: "Argentina" Roll 11, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 104, Reel 14)
    - 38: "Argentina" Roll 7, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 104, Reel 15)
    - 39: "Argentina" Roll 10, 8/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 104, Reel 16)
    - 20: "Argentina" Roll 37, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 105, Reel 1)
    - 21: "Argentina" Roll 40, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 105, Reel 2)
    - 41: "Argentina" Roll 34, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 105, Reel 3)
    - 45: "Argentina" Roll 9, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 105, Reel 4)
    - 46: "Argentina" Roll 31, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 105, Reel 5)
    - 49: "Argentina" Roll 81, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 105, Reel 6)
    - 52: "Argentina" Roll 58, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 105, Reel 7)
    - 61: "Argentina" Roll 46, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 105, Reel 8)
    - 62: "Argentina" Roll 85¯9, 6/1985; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 105, Reel 9)
    - 63: "Argentina" Roll 85¯8, 6/1985; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 105, Reel 10)
    - 69: "Argentina" Roll 12, 8/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 105, Reel 11)
    - 73: "Argentina" Roll 26, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 105, Reel 12)
    - 74: "Argentina" Roll 29, 3/1984; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 105, Reel 13)
    - 75: "Las Madres" Roll #6, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 105, Reel 14)
    - 77: "Argentina" Roll 85¯7, 6/1985; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 105, Reel 15)
    - 78: "Las Madres", nd; 1.0 Items; Film: Film Outs; Color Negative; 400 ft. (Carton 105, Reel 16)
    - "Las Madres" ¯ exhibition print, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: Exhibition Print; Color Positive w/ sound; 2000 ft. (Oversize-box 107, Reel 1)
    - "Las Madres ¯ English" ¯ exhibition print, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: Exhibition Print; Color Positive w/ sound; 2000 ft. (Oversize-box 107, Reel 2)
    - "Las Madres ¯ English Magnetic Track", nd; 1.0 Items; Audio: Dub; 16mm Full Coat Magnetic Stock; 2300 ft. (Oversize-box 108, Reel 1)
    - "Las Madres ¯ 16mm sound mix ¯ Spanish Version", 1.0 Items; Audio: Dub; 16mm Full Coat Magnetic Stock; 2000 ft. (Oversize-box 108, Reel 2)
    - "Las Madres Film Project", nd; 1.0 Items; Film: Exhibition Print; Color Positive w/ sound; 2000 ft. (Oversize-box 109, Reel 1)
    - Las Madres Film Outs: 79, 83, 85, 86, 87, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: Trims; Color Negative; 1000 ft. (Carton 114, Reel 1)
    - Las Madres Film Outs: 88, 89, 89A, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: Trims; Color Negative; 1000 ft. (Carton 114, Reel 2)
    - Las Madres Film Outs: 80, 81, 82, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: Trims; Color Negative; 1000 ft. (Carton 114, Reel 3)
    - Las Madres Film Outs: 90, 91, 92, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: Trims; Color Negative; 1000 ft. (Carton 114, Reel 4)
    - Las Madres Film Outs: 93, 94, 96, 97, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: Trims; Color Negative; 1000 ft. (Carton 114, Reel 5)
    - Las Madres Film Outs: 98, 99; Pulled Shots, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: Trims; Color Negative; 1000 ft. (Carton 114, Reel 6)
    - Misc Rolls: (Sherman Grind (?)¯43294, I.P. ¯ "Peron", A (Blk & Wht)¯42185, OPT. S.T., Pulled Shots for Titles), 1.0 Items; Film: Trims; Color Negative (Rolls 1,2,5) and B&W Negative (3,4); 1000 ft. (Carton 114, Reel 7)
    - "Madres" ¯ Pulled Shot Still, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: Trims; 16mm; Color Negative; >50 ft. (Carton 114, Reel 8)
  - La Ofrenda: The Days of the Dead, 1988
    - Que Viva La Muerte (excerpts in no particular order), 10/1988; 1.0 Items; Video: VHS; Dub; 13 min. (Carton 79, Videotape 8)
    - "La Ofrenda ¯ The Days of the Dead", 1.0 Items; Video: VHS; Dub; 00:56:21 (Carton 79, Videotape 9)
    - "La Ofrenda ¯ The Days of the Dead" ¯ Film Transfer, 1.0 Items; Video: VHS; Dub; 00:56:21 (Carton 79, Videotape 10)
    - [Untitled Tape], nd; 1.0 Items; Video: VHS; Dub; ~5 min. (Carton 79, Videotape 11)
    - "La Ofrenda" ¯ Old Version (Fine Cut), 12/1988; 1.0 Items; Video: VHS; Dub; ~120 min. (Carton 79, Videotape 12)
    - Dia De La Muerte ¯ 80 Minute Assembly, nd; 1.0 Items; Video: VHS; Dub; ~80 min. (Carton 79, Videotape 13)
    - "La Ofrenda", 1.0 Items; Video: VHS; Dub; ~60 min. (Carton 79, Videotape 14)
    - "La Ofrenda ¯ The Days of the Dead" ¯ Film Transfer for preview only, 1.0 Items; Video: VHS; Dub; 00:56:21 (Carton 79, Videotape 15)
    - Dia De Los Muertos ¯ Russ. Hill W.P. Transfer, nd; 1.0 Items; Video: VHS; Dub; ~120 min. (Carton 79, Videotape 16)
    - The Day of the Dead excerpts, nd; 1.0 Items; Video: VHS; Dub; ~120 min. (Carton 79, Videotape 17)
    - "La Ofrenda ¯ The Days of the Dead", 1.0 Items; Video: VHS; Dub; 00:56:21 (Carton 79, Videotape 18)
    - La Ofrenda Unfinished Fine Cut, 1.0 Items; Video: VHS; Dub; ~120 min. (Carton 79, Videotape 19)